var questionsConfig = {
    mButton: {
        Q1: {
            question: "12 X 9 = ",
            answer: 108,
        },
        Q2: {
            question: "25 X 7 = ",
            answer: 175,
        },
        Q3: {
            question: "17 X 11 = ",
            answer: 187,
        },
        Q4: {
            question: "108 X 2 = ",
            answer: 216,
        },
        Q5: {
            question: "(5x3) X 300 = ",
            answer: 4500,
        },
        Q6: {
            question: "12 X (500x2) = ",
            answer: 12000,
        },
        Q7: {
            question: "702 X (0.5x20) = ",
            answer: 7020,
        },
        Q8: {
            question: "(400x2) X (0.25x40) = ",
            answer: 8000,
        }

    },
    dButton: {
        Q1: {
            question: "36 / 2 = ",
            answer: 18,
        },
        Q2: {
            question: "100 / 0.1 = ",
            answer: 10,
        },
        Q3: {
            question: "963 / 3 = ",
            answer: 321,
        },
        Q4: {
            question: "144 / 12 = ",
            answer: 12,
        },
        Q5: {
            question: "45 / 3 = ",
            answer: 15,
        },
        Q6: {
            question: "(81/1) / 3 = ",
            answer: 27,
        },
        Q7: {
            question: "(36/2) / 0.5 = ",
            answer: 36,
        },
        Q8: {
            question: "(90/0.5) / (28/7) = ",
            answer: 45,
        }
    },
    aButton: {
        Q1: {
            question: "12.5 + 21.5 = ",
            answer: 34,
        },
        Q2: {
            question: "96 + 69 = ",
            answer: 165,
        },
        Q3: {
            question: "179.1 + 1.9 = ",
            answer: 181,
        },
        Q4: {
            question: "(123+77) + 321 = ",
            answer: 521,
        },
        Q5: {
            question: "(13.5+57.5) + 79 = ",
            answer: 150,
        },
        Q6: {
            question: "(313.2+86.8) + 101 = ",
            answer: 501,
        },
        Q7: {
            question: "(21.6+61.4) + 21 + 12 = ",
            answer: 116,
        },
        Q8: {
            question: "(36+63) + (44+77) = ",
            answer: 220,
        }
    },
    sButton: {
        Q1: {
            question: "90 - 7 = ",
            answer: 83,
        },
        Q2: {
            question: "43 - 34 = ",
            answer: 9,
        },
        Q3: {
            question: "369 - 135 = ",
            answer: 234,
        },
        Q4: {
            question: "1007 - 701 = ",
            answer: 306,
        },
        Q5: {
            question: "1503.3 - 307.3 = ",
            answer: 1196,
        },
        Q6: {
            question: "7878 - 2323 = ",
            answer: 5555,
        },
        Q7: {
            question: "852 - 147 = ",
            answer: 705,
        },
        Q8: {
            question: "9753.13 - 8642.13 = ",
            answer: 1111,
        }
    }
};